http://www.mercomarine.com/terms-and-conditions/

Effective Date: 9/10/2019
Welcome to Merco Marine! This agreement (“Agreement” or the “Terms of Service”) describes the terms on which Merco, Inc. (DBA Merco Marine) offers you the ability to use our web site and all aspects there in. This includes but is not limited to products, purchasing, technical data, contact information, articles, links, pricing information, & product codes. This offer is conditioned on your agreement to all of the terms and conditions contained in the Terms of Service, including the policies and terms linked to or otherwise referenced in this Agreement.
By using Merco Marine, you agree to and accept these Terms of Service. If you do not so agree, you should decline this Agreement and discontinue further use of our web services.
Merco Inc. respects the privacy of our visitors to our web site. At no time do we sell or share information collected from our site to any company or individual. Merco Inc DBA Merco Marine has established the following policy to help its customers and visitors of this site understand the way we conduct business. The policy covers the topics listed as follows:
Information Collection and Use
Statistics
Collection of Information
Online Ordering
Use of Information
Site Communications
Product Bulletins and/or Special Offers
Sharing
1.A Statistics
We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, and databases to create statistics of what our users are looking for. The statistics log is standard with most web site servers. Specific information we look for in the statistics log includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/ exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. We use this information to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the site, and gather broad demographic information for site use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.
1.B Collection of Information
Merco Marine is the sole owner of the information collected on our web site. We collect information from our users at several different points on our web site.
1.C Online Ordering
We request information from users on our online order form. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to complete customer orders. If we have trouble processing an order, the information provided will be used to contact a user.
1.D Use of Information
In addition to billing purposes, you agree that Merco Marine has the right to use your personal purchase Information for its own internal marketing purposes.
2. Site Communications
2.A Product Bulletins and/or Special Offers
Established members may occasionally receive information on products, services, special offers, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to accept or decline these communication types.
3. Sharing
3.A Links
This web site may contain links to other web sites. Please be aware that we, Merco Marine, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware of when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected on our website.
3.B Business Transitions
In the event Merco Marine goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, user’s personal information, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.
3.C Legal
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required to by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our web site.
3.D Security
Merco Marine takes every precaution to protect our user’s information (such as credit card number, etc.) When users submit sensitive information via our web site, their information is protected both online and offline.
When our order form asks users to enter sensitive information, that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry – SSL. Before entering a secure page, such as our order form where personal information is being requested, the lock icon on the bottom of web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked. You will most likely see some type of “locked” symbol somewhere on your browser to let you know that you are viewing a secured portion of our web site.
While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user information offline. All of our user information, not just sensitive information, is restricted to our office. We maintain a physical paper copy of all information from online orders in a secure location in our office. We also keep a digital copy of the information in an offline computer system that has no wired or wireless connection to the internet. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information.
4. Lost or Damaged Goods
YOU SHOULD THOROUGHLY INSPECT YOUR SHIPMENT AT THE TIME IT IS RECEIVED!
The material was carefully counted, packaged and properly loaded for shipment when accepted by the carrier.
In the event of any loss or damage, the delivery receipt MUST BE SIGNED AND NOTED AS SUCH. You must also notify us within 5 business days so that we may go over what is missing or damaged on your order and we can then follow up with the carrier and put in a claim for the merchandise. If preceding conditions are not met, the transportation company will not entertain any claim for loss or damage. Your acceptance of a shipment that is short or in damaged condition without proper notation is done at your own risk.
After an inspection report and claim have been submitted to the carrier, you MUST RETAIN the material for possible carrier pickup, prior to the payment of the claim.
Once we have received a copy of the delivery receipt with your signature we then will ship out replacement material if the situation permits.
Note: Claims for loss or damage must not be deducted from our invoice, nor payment be withheld.
If users have any questions, problems, or changes about information provided on our web site they can email merco@mercomarine.com.
5. Returns
You can return new, unopened items from a cancelled order within 2 weeks after they have been delivered to you. Items are to be re-packed in an undamaged box of the same size as which the products arrived prior to shipping. There is a 15 PERCENT restocking fee on ALL returned items.
6. Discounts and Specials
Occasionally we offer discounts and coupons to our customers. All orders must be paid and shipped by the end of the sale. When the sale only applies to certain products the discount will be automatically deducted from each item when you order on our web site. We also occasionally offer a coupon code for a percentage or an ammount of money to be deducted from the order total. Coupon codes are always found on our home page when they are available to everyone. Any specail offer is not valid on previously placed orders.
SIMPLE & FAST
SHIPPING100% US-BASED
MANUFACTURINGEXPERIENCED
SERVICE & SUPPORT
Featured Products
Inside Corner - HD
0 out of 5 $28.81
Outside Corner Male - HD
Get all the latest information on Events, Sales and Offers.
Sign up for newsletter today.
*
NameThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
© Copyright 2020. Merco Marine, Inc.
All Rights Reserved.
